迪克森
Dixon!
他们让你上屋顶
They're looking for you on the roof.
两位  你们懂我的难处吧
Guys, you see my problem here.
这可不好看
This is not a good look.
这让我们都很难办
It puts all of us in a very tough spot.
不管有没有难处  这都是真相
Problem or not, it's the truth.
那我们再捋一遍  确保我没搞错
So, let's just run through this one more time, make sure I got it straight.
你们进去  一言不合交火了
You went in. Things got tense. A firefight broke out.
然后这里的人杀光了
Then the people here killed every last one
我们训练有素  全副武装的士兵
of our trained, armed, and armored soldiers,
但没杀你俩
but not you two,
一个独臂男和一个神父
the one-armed guy and the priest.
然后凶手们逃了
Then the killers escaped.
你们用对讲机呼了我
You called me over the walkie.
我们开车过来
We drove up.
就是这样
And here we are.
这就是你们的故事
That's your story?
-差不多吧  -对
That's basically it, yeah. Yeah. - Yeah. Yes.
你对此怎么看
What do you think about all this?
我们在外漂泊了很久
Well, we've been on the road a long time.
他们很有实力
They can definitely handle themselves.
既然他们这么说  那这就是事实
If that's what they say happened, that's what happened.
也许吧
Maybe.
但我有另一个理论  听好了
But I have another theory. Just hear me out.
一群癫狂暴力的陌生人放过你们
It doesn't make a whole lot of sense for a bunch of crazed, violent strangers
实在说不太通
to just keep the two of you alive.
但你们也不会说谎
It also doesn't make sense for the two of you to lie
去保护一群癫狂暴力的陌生人
to protect a bunch of crazed, violent strangers --
除非  他们不是陌生人
unless they weren't strangers.
你是说我们在撒谎吗
Are you calling us liars?
你的人没控制住局面
Your guy lost control of the situation.
我们勉强才活了下来
We barely survived.
别把责任推到我们身上
We're not gonna take the fall for this.
好吧  有道理
Okay. Fair enough.
我不想激怒你们  我只是要完成工作
I'm not trying to ruffle any feathers here. I've just got a job to do.
归根结底  我们都想要同样的东西
At the end of the day, we all want the same thing, right?
伸张正义
Justice.
那当然
Of course.
你俩继续搜查这里  我们其他人出发了
You two keep searching the area while the rest of us move out.
-收到  长官  -回联邦吗
- Copy that, sir. - To the Commonwealth?
不  这帮禽兽仍逍遥法外
Oh, no. There's monsters running loose.
我们要把他们揪出来
We need to smoke them out.
先去山顶寨
We'll start with the hilltop,
看我们的朋友是否知道些什么
see if our friends heard anything.
至少应该让他们知道
At the very least, they should know
有一些很危险的人可能会去他们那里
there's some very dangerous people who might be coming their way.
穿上盔甲吧  士兵
Better suit up, soldier.
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十五集
早上好
Good morning.
昨晚真有趣
Last night was fun.
前晚也一样
And the night before.
是啊
Yeah.
我们的性生活真和谐
We're pretty awesome at this sex thing.
我当然懂了  我做过很多爱
And I should know. I've had a lot of sex in my life.
没有做过很多
Well... not a lot of sex.
等等  你猜怎么着
Wait. You know what?
我们都是成年人
We're both adults.
我做过很多爱  你做过很多爱
I've had a lot of sex, and you've had a lot of sex.
我真喜欢听你说话
I love listening to you talk.
也喜欢和你做爱
And, of course, the sex.
我也是
Me, too.
但哥们  这一大清早的
But, dude, these crack-of-dawn,
超级战士早起闹铃太烦人了
super-soldier wake-up times suck ass.
我都不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you do it.
你到底需要睡眠吗  我每次转身
Do you even need sleep? 'Cause every time I roll over,
都能看见你躺在那里  盯着天花板
you're just lying there staring at the ceiling.
我认为你是个半机器人
I think you're part robot.
对
That's it.
被你发现了
You got me.
哔  哔  哔
Beep. Beep, beep.
说吧
Come on.
怎么回事
What's the deal with that?
你是在冥想吗
Is it some kind of meditation?
也许我只是沉浸在喜悦中
Maybe I'm just basking in the afterglow.
我睡眠很好
I sleep fine.
我确实对别人有这个影响
I do have that effect on people.
但那看起来不像喜悦  更像是煎熬
But it didn't really look like basking, more like...stewing.
你想说什么
You getting at something?
没什么  只想确保你没事
No. Just making sure you're cool.
好吧
Okay, then.
我没事
I'm fine.
很好
Great.
非常好
Totally.
但如果你有什么话想一吐为快...
But if there was anything you needed to get off your chest...
我只是想说  与大家想的不同
...all I'm saying is that, contrary to popular opinion,
我其实很擅长倾听
I'm pretty freaking great at listening.
我说了我没事
I said I'm fine.
听到了  清清楚楚
Message received loud and clear.
看吧
See?
我很擅长倾听
Good at listening.
你上班要迟到了
You're gonna be late for work.
进来
Come in.
抱歉一大早叫你们过来
Apologies for the early-morning invite.
这场谈话不能公之于众
This discussion isn't quite ready for public broadcast.
你们没事吧
Are you two okay?
那条信息感觉很紧急
That message seemed pretty urgent.
罗西塔告诉我了一件
Rosita confided in me
她最近在工作中遇到的惨剧
about a harrowing experience she recently encountered on the job.
我们认为应该将这件事
We thought it would be beneficial,
告诉你这位愿意讲真话的记者
given your position as a truth-telling newsperson, to give you the deets.
好  发生了什么
Alright, so, what's up?
塞巴斯蒂安和他的几位亲信
Sebastian and some of his cronies
强迫达里尔和我去
forced Daryl and I to steal cash
边界外的一座废弃的房子偷现金
from an abandoned house outside the perimeter.
在那里  有个女人
There was a woman there.
他们以前就做过这种事
They had done this before.
他们派过平民去那里  那些人都死了
They had sent civilians in, and none of them made it out alive.
他们要我们别声张
They wanted us to stay quiet,
但我很在意那个女人  爱普尔
but I think about that woman, April,
还有他们经历过的事
and what they all went through.
这里还是有好人的
There are good people here.
他们应该知道真相
They need to know the truth.
那个前士兵失踪后
Someone sent us a list of names of people
有人给了我们一张名单
when the ex-trooper went missing.
我们试过解读它
We tried to figure it out,
但一直没有头绪
but we just kept hitting dead ends.
爱普尔·马顿斯  可能是她  对吧
April Martens. That could be her, right?
让我看看
Let me see that.
不  这个名单上人太多了
No, there are way more names on this list
塞巴斯蒂安没派这么多人去房子
than Sebastian sent into that house.
可能有关联  但应该是别的事
Maybe it's related, but there's something else going on here.
不管是什么事
Whatever this is,
只要与弥尔顿一家有关
if the Miltons are involved,
相关的文件就会被锁起来
they'll keep it locked up.
我们需要内线挖掘情报
We need inside access to dig it out.
我可能认识一个人
I might know someone.
东西都带齐了吗
You got everything you need?
-应该吧  -很好
- I think so. - Good.
我会确保小瑞今天准时上课
And I'll make sure RJ gets to his classes on time today.
好  最好如此
Alright. Well, you better.
-走吧  慢性子  -给
- Come on, slowpoke. - Here you go.
以西结
Ezekiel.
日安  少年们
Good day, young friends.
畅饮知识之杯
Drink deep from the cup of knowledge
听老师的话
and listen to your teachers.
好了  快走吧
Alright, go on. Here you go.
-谢谢  -拜
- Thank you. - Bye.
拜
Bye!
你看起来真有活力
You're looking lively.
切掉一个柚子大小的肿瘤有神奇的效果
Well, losing a tumor the size of a grapefruit works wonders.
恢复得还好吗
Recovery's going well?
还得慢慢恢复  但预后诊断良好
Still got a ways to go, but prognosis is good.
痊愈得很好
Healing well.
我考虑了你之前说的话
Yeah, I was thinking about what you said before.
还有我当时的反应
How I reacted.
我一直没有正式感谢你
I never properly thanked you.
你没必要感谢我
You don't have to thank me.
-有必要  -不
- I do. - No.
我无法想象你为这事费了多大劲
Can't imagine the lengths you went to to make this happen.
我至少该说声"谢谢"
Least I can do is say "Thank you."
我最近没闲着
I've been busy.
-是吗  -是
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我把你的话牢记在心
I took your words to heart about
用获得的时间多做一些事
doing something extra with this time I've been given.
你有空的话  我想带你去看看
I'd love to show you if you're free.
今天我很忙
Today's tough.
今天不行
Can't do it today.
拜托
Come on.
-不  我说真的  -跟我一起翘班吧
- No, really -- - Play hooky with me.
不行  我工作特忙
Ah, I can't. I'm swamped at work.
面包店的工作吗
At the bakery?
不是
Um, well, no.
我找了另一份工作
Um, I got another job.
有件事我必须...
It's just this thing I had to --
这...
Um, it's a --
这很复杂
It's -- It's complicated.
出了一件事  一切都乱套了
And something happened, and then things went all sideways.
-卡萝尔  -我必须去...
- Carol. - And I have to go --
我得先想办法纠正一件事
I just have some things that I need to figure out first, to fix.
你不知道这件事最好  好吗
Uh, it's better that you don't even know about it, okay?
相信我
Just trust me.
我相信你
I trust you...
胜过任何人
more than anyone.
本以为这地方会让生活更简单
You'd think this place would make life easier?
结果这里却更压抑
Feels like there's a lot more gray instead.
下次去
Rain check?
说定了
Guaranteed.
我恢复健康了  你甩不掉我了
I'm getting healthy again. You're stuck with me.
这我能接受
I guess I can live with that.
拜
Bye.
你俩去处理吧
Why don't you two take care of this?
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
我们必须节省弹药
We have to save our ammunition.
我听说你俩挺有实力
I was told you can handle yourselves.
有什么问题吗
Where's the problem?
给你省了子弹
We saved you a bullet.
而且几乎没出汗
And barely broke a sweat!
厉害
Nice!
走吧  继续前进
Come on, let's keep moving!
戴上头盔  士兵
Helmet on, soldier.
不是时候吗
This a bad time?
今天不太顺
Not the best day,
但是  请进
but, um, please come in.
你感觉还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
-是不是有什么...   -不是
- Is there something -- - No, no.
我很好
I'm great.
我是为了一个朋友来的
This is about a friend of mine.
她病了  没钱治疗
She's sick and can't afford the treatment.
不想让家人负债
Won't put her family into debt.
她需要动个小手术
She needs a small procedure.
如果我们能在体制外解决这事...
If we can take care of it outside the system --
什么样的手术
W-What sort of procedure?
阑尾切除术
Appendectomy.
-以西结  -我已经准备好了设备
- Ezekiel -- - I've secured the equipment
和无菌手术区
and a sterile operating area.
我还需要一点物资  以及
I just need a few extra supplies and...
你
you.
以西结  这很冒险
Ezekiel, this is incredibly risky.
-我懂  -不只是对她来说
- I understand that. - And -- And not just for her.
所有牵扯其中的人都有危险
For -- For everyone involved.
她不会改变主意
She's not gonna change her mind,
我了解有多大风险
and I understand the risks.
她也了解
She does, too.
她只能这样做  不然我不会来找你
I wouldn't ask if this wasn't her best option.
我今早失去了一个病人
I lost a patient this morning.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
那还是在这里
And that was here.
在这里  以西结  在医院里
That was here, Ezekiel, in a hospital.
托米  只有你能做到这件事
Tomi... you're the only one that can do this.
拜托了
Please.
为社区安全尽你的一份力
Do your part to keep our community safe.
发现问题  及时报告
If you see something, say something.
记住  我们祸福与共
Remember, we are all in this together.
你来这里做什么  我们不能被看到在一起
What are you doing here? We shouldn't be seen together.
紧急情况需要立刻见面
Circumstances required an immediate face-to-face.
我有所防备  看到了吗
I took precautions -- see?
我只是个卑微的送货员
Just a humble delivery boy.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你要我找秘密文件吗
You want me to look for secret files?
对  偷走它们
Yes, and steal them.
尤金  我们应该远离麻烦
Eugene, we're supposed to be staying out of trouble,
而不是去找麻烦
not looking for it.
霍恩斯比的事终于顺利了
Things have finally been going right with Hornsby,
亚历山大也在平稳重建中
and the Alexandria rebuild is coming along.
我的朋友们别无选择
My friends didn't have a choice.
罗西塔是被塞巴斯蒂安逼的
Rosita was forced into the situation by Sebastian.
等等
Wait.
这与弥尔顿一家有关吗
This involves the Miltons?
至少与那个年轻的疯子有关
The young psychopath, at least.
好吧
Okay, um,
你应该先说这点的
you could have led with that bit of information.
麦克斯  有人死了
Max, people have died.
更多人失踪了  你哥哥能证实
More are missing. Your brother can corroborate.
迈克尔
Michael?
他当时也在场
He was there, too.
抱歉打扰  女士
Oh, um, sorry to interrupt, ma'am.
不  没事
No. Not at all.
你用这个房间吧
Um, the room is all yours.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
给  祝你今天愉快
There you go. Have a nice day.
下午好  玛姬
Afternoon, Maggie.
很高兴再见
Good to see you again.
你想要什么
What do you want?
有一群杀人犯在逃
There are some killers on the loose.
我们损失了很多人
We lost a lot of men.
我正在找他们
So I'm hunting them down.
还有他们偷走的货物
And the property they stole,
联邦的货物
the Commonwealth's property.
我对此一无所知
I don't know anything about that.
那当然
Well, of course not.
所以你不介意我们四处看看吧
So you wouldn't mind if we just do a quick look around, right?
排除你们的嫌疑
Rule you all out.
为了交报告
For the paperwork.
我已经回答过你了
I gave you my answer.
你强行进去会害死人的
You're gonna get people killed if you force your way in there.
她没给我别的选择
She isn't giving me much of a choice here.
我去跟她谈谈
I'll talk to her.
你为什么要这样做
And why would you do that?
因为我今天不想对任何人开枪
Because I don't want to shoot anybody here today.
让我去谈
Let me do this.
我们进去  无人受伤
We go in, nobody gets hurt.
可以吗
Deal?
可以
Deal.
开门
Open up.
不必这样
It doesn't have to be this way.
必须这样
Yeah, it does.
他们不检查是不会走的
Ain't nobody leaving until they look around.
会很快的  我保证
It'll be quick, I promise.
你希望我信任他吗
You expect me to trust him?
我没让你信任他
I ain't asking you to trust him.
我让你信任我
I'm asking you to trust me.
你要告诉我发生了什么吗
You gonna tell me what's going on?
你要说得更具体点
I'm gonna need you to be more specific.
塞巴斯蒂安  盗窃行动
Uh, Sebastian, a heist,
失踪的人
people missing?
听起来你已经知道了
Sounds like you already know.
但我要听你亲口说
But I want to hear it from you.
这种事你为什么要瞒着我
Why would you keep something like this from me?
因为这不关你的事
'Cause it's not your business.
你想听什么
I mean, what you want to hear?
这地方不完美吗
This place ain't perfect?
我们有幸拥有过去的世界  包括它的缺点
That we're lucky to have some parts of the old world, warts and all?
这些都不是什么新鲜事
Ain't none of this shit new.
人们互相伤害  人们互相残杀
People hurt each other. People kill each other.
这是常事  这是工作的一部分
Happens all the time. It's part of the job.
怎么  所以一切都是对的吗
And what? That's just supposed to make everything okay?
不  当然不对
No. Of course not.
人们失去了生命  因为我辜负了他们
People lost their lives because I failed them.
我大意了
I missed it.
这是我的责任  不是你的
The weight of that is mine to carry, not yours.
我不是个小孩子了  迈克尔
I'm not a little kid anymore, Mike.
你不用当大哥哥
You don't need to play big brother
保护我免受世界的伤害
and protect me from the world.
说这话的小姑娘
Says the little girl
几个月前用无电线还差点被发现了
who almost got caught on the radio a few months ago.
这不公平
Okay, that's not fair.
我不想跟你吵架
Look, I don't want to fight with you.
那就让我帮你
Then let me help you.
你想帮忙吗
You want to help?
别管这事了
Let it go.
已经结束了  我处理完了
It's over. I fixed it.
那塞巴斯蒂安呢
And what about Sebastian?
你不是已经知道了吗  行了吧
Again, you already know. Come on, now.
你怎么能容忍那个小混蛋逍遥法外
How are you okay with letting that little bastard walk free?
因为我还要担心其余五万人的性命
Because I got 50,000 other lives to think about.
得了吧
Oh, please.
如果我去查那个小子  会发生什么呢
So, I go after the kid, what happens then?
你觉得他们会无视这种违逆吗
You think that kind of insubordination is gonna slide?
然后呢
Then what?
我消失了怎么办
What if I disappear?
谁来维持这个地方的运作
Who keeps this place running?
如果联邦完蛋了
If the Commonwealth falls,
死的人会比那房子里的人多得多
a lot more people are gonna wind up dead than the ones in that house.
不是所有人都认为人命是可接受的损失
Not all of us view human lives as acceptable losses.
帕梅拉也是你的老板
Pam's your boss, too.
你去跟她说
Take it up with her.
你说话她听
You got her ear.
嗯  而你说话联邦听
Yeah, and you've got the community's.
他们听你的
They listen to you.
他们仰慕你  仰头就能看到你
They look up to you -- literally.
我只是个兵
I am just a soldier.
但你能成为更重要的人
But you could be so much more.
你能改变这个地方
You could change this place.
但也许是我太天真了
But maybe that's just me being naive.
也许你只是一张海报
Maybe you are really just a poster.
尽你的一份力
好了
Good.
他们应该很快会走
They should move on in a minute.
然后我们就去装卸区
Then we head for the loading dock.
作为一个害怕打破常规的人
For a guy who was worried about coloring outside the lines,
你应对得很好
you're handling it well --
甚至有点享受
maybe even enjoying it.
我也曾打破规矩
I've broken my share of rules once upon a time.
我妹妹能作证
My sister can attest to that.
但这地方使人安逸
But this place has a way of lulling you.
既然安全  何必找事  对吧
Why upset the applecart if it's keeping you safe, right?
的确难以抉择
That is the struggle --
保护自己  还是保护别人
protecting ourselves or others?
我希望两者都能保护
I wouldn't mind both.
-好了吗  -嗯
- Ready? - Yeah.
糟了
Shit.
车不错
Nice truck!
还在用吗
This new?
我试过转换发动机  但发动不起来
I started converting the engine, but it doesn't run.
知道我们在现场发现了轮胎印吗
You know we found tire tracks at the scene?
如今没有多少能发动的车了
Not a lot of cars running these days.
你想说什么就直说吧
You got something you want to say, why don't you just say it?
我只是在说事实
Just stating the facts.
我出身于机械世家
You know, I come from a long line of gearheads.
你介意吗
You mind?
作为一辆久放在这里的车来说  它真干净
She sure is clean for a truck that just sits here.
乙醇转换没问题
Ethanol conversion is solid.
进气系统看起来挺好
Intake looks good.
我们上次来的时候留了很多燃料
We left plenty of fuel the last time we were here.
难怪发动不起来
No wonder she won't work.
起动继电器断开了
The starter relay is disconnected.
我只用
I'll just... go ahead
帮你接上
and hook that back up for you.
来试试吧
Let's test it out,
看我是否宝刀未老
see if I've got the magic touch.
你和你的人可以搜到日落
You and your people have 'til sundown.
然后就走吧
Then you can be on your way.
天啊
Oh, God.
他们交给我吧
I can handle them from here.
感谢你谨慎处理
Thanks for the discretion.
我还希望你的新工作在这里有人脉
I was hoping this new job of yours had connections here.
我或许提了你的名字
I might have mentioned your name.
嗯  我父亲常说
Yeah, well, my old man used to say,
"杀死你的就是希望"
"It's the hope that kills you."
我们是不是完了
Are we screwed?
我不适合蹲监狱
I don't do well in confinement.
别担心
Don't -- Don't worry.
我处理好了
I've got it handled.
除非你今天还打算惹更多麻烦
Unless you plan on getting in more trouble today?
麻烦不一定都是坏的
Not all trouble is bad trouble.
来看看吧
Come see.
我们已经让你翘班了
We already pulled you out of work.
多耽误几分钟又何妨
What's a few more minutes?
以西结  求你告诉我  你的朋友是人类
Ezekiel, please tell me your friend is human.
兽医治疗区
来  给
Go ahead. Here.
以西结
Hey, Ezekiel.
天啊
Wow.
你确实没闲着
You really have been busy.
我要还人情
I've got a debt to repay.
我的病人已经来了吗
Is my patient already here?
-特丽萨在后面  -以西结
- Theresa's in the back. - Hey, Zeke.
能占用你一分钟吗
You got a minute?
为了你
For you?
我有两分钟
I got two.
我想为之前的事道歉
I-I wanted to apologize -- for earlier.
我是第一次经历这种事
This whole thing is new to me.
我不是说性生活  而是
I-I mean, not the sex part, but, uh...
我们的关系
...us.
我不想...
And, uh, I don't want to --
听好了
Okay, listen.
我对不对劲的人
I got a special sense
有种特殊的感觉
for when somebody's... not okay.
我有过很多亲身经历
A lot of firsthand experience.
我表面上可能很性感
And I might put out this totally sexy,
无忧无虑  乐观开朗
carefree, fun-times vibe,
但我也能应付沉重的事
but I can handle heavy stuff, too.
假如
In -- In case...
你需要倾诉的话
you ever need it.
我杀了两个手下
I killed two of my men.
掩盖了罪行
And I covered it up.
我从没想过我会成为这种人
Never thought I'd be that guy.
我不是这样的人
That's not how I came up.
我父母不是这样教育我的
That's not how my parents raised me.
我有一些绝对不会逾越的底线
I had certain lines that I didn't let myself cross...
直到现在
until now.
你知道我最苦恼的是什么事吗
You know the thing that's really messing with my head?
让我夜不能寐  耿耿于怀的是什么事吗
The thing that keeps me up at night, the thing I keep thinking?
我会再做一次
I'd do it again.
我花了很长时间
I spent a long time,
一辈子都在努力撑着
all my life trying to keep it together,
让其他人觉得安全可靠
safe, solid for everyone else.
我只懂这件事
It's the only thing I know.
我只会这件事
Only thing I'm good at.
我成功了  这让我们走到了现在
And it worked. It got us this far.
也许这地方需要一些别的东西
Maybe this place needs something else.
也许我成了问题的一部分
Maybe I'm part of the problem.
我不知道  我只是累了
I don't know. I'm just tired.
我们何不进屋去
Why don't we... go inside
一起想办法
and we figure it out together.
赫谢尔  对吧
Hershel, right?
我是兰斯
I'm Lance.
不知道你是否记得我
Don't know if you remember me.
我听说你的人生很刺激  少年
I've heard you've had a pretty exciting life, young man.
最近有什么刺激的旅行吗
Taken any exciting trips lately?
那你妈妈呢
How about your mom?
赫谢尔  我最不希望这里出事
The last thing I want, Hershel, is for something to happen here,
尤其不希望你妈妈出事
especially to your mom.
所以我需要你的帮助
So I'm gonna need your help.
如果我能知道真相  我就能改正一些事
If I can get the truth, I can fix things.
这是我的工作
That's what I do.
但如果人们有小秘密
But I can't keep people safe
我就没法保护他们了
if they keep secrets.
所以我需要你仔细想想
So I want you to think really hard here.
你有没有什么想告诉我的事
Is there anything you want to tell me?
我应该去找我妈妈了
I should probably go get my mom.
等等
Hey, hold on a second.
你是个好孩子  很勇敢
You're a good kid... brave.
好孩子
And the thing about good kids is...
应该得到礼物
they deserve presents.
说来有趣
It's funny.
我在发生坏事的地方发现了这顶帽子
I found this hat all the way back where the bad things happened.
这么好的帽子浪费了就可惜了
Be a shame for a-a nice hat like this to go to waste.
真没想到
I'll be damned.
完全合适
Perfect fit.
怎么这么巧
What are the odds?
放开他  不然我们会开枪
Release him or we will shoot.
快走
Let's go! Move, move!
这家伙对赫谢尔动手了
This guy put his hands on Hershel.
他说会发生坏事
He said something bad was gonna happen.
-我可以解释  -退后  快点
- I can explain. - Back up! Now!
我是个好人  玛姬
You know, I'm a nice guy, Maggie.
我甚至会允许你们放下武器
I'll even let you back down
不让任何人受伤
so no one gets hurt.
很多人都犯过威胁我家人的错误
Plenty others have made the mistake of threatening my family.
他们中大部分人都已经死了
Most of them are dead now.
你把这地方翻了个底朝天  什么都没找到
And you turned this place upside down and you found nothing.
如果你不想白白送死
So unless you want to die for nothing,
就让他们放下枪
tell them to drop the guns
趁还没有完全失控之前
before something really fucking bad happens.
所有人放下武器
Everyone lower your weapons.
这是命令
That's an order.
退后
Back up.
我们要走了
We're leaving.
如果有任何误会  我很抱歉
Sorry if there was any miscommunication.
很遗憾我们不能成为朋友
Shame we couldn't be friends.
我们不回联邦
We ain't going back to the Commonwealth.
他们让我们在外面继续搜索
They're keeping us out here to search.
直到找到杀人犯吗
Until they find the killers?
对
Yeah.
既然不能交出杀人犯
Well, if we can't give them the killers,
那么枪呢
what about those guns?
我们找到枪  也许能争取点时间
We find them, maybe it buys us some time.
那可未必
That's a big maybe.
要出事了
Something's about to go down.
注意一点
Just keep your eyes open.
有什么发现吗
You find something?
-是的  -带我去看
- We did. - Show me.
你做得很好
You did good.
大部分辛苦工作都是西奥做的
Theo did most of the hard work.
但我必须承认
I have to admit, though...
感觉很特别
it feels special.
我们经历了那么多
After all we've been though,
这是我最接近
as close as I came...
新开始的一次
...got a fresh start.
对我来说  重要的是让我的朋友知道
And it was important to me that my friend know
我有多感激她
just how much I appreciate her.
那感觉一定非常好
It must feel really, really good.
你是怎么了
What's going on in there?
只是在想这个世界
Just thinking about the world.
这也太宽泛了
That's a big subject.
具体是什么
Anything specific?
只是...  这么多年...
Just... all the years...
这么多黑暗
the darkness.
经历了那么多
After everything,
仍在经历这么多
in the midst of everything,
而你坐在这里  精神焕发
you're sitting here glowing.
光明适合你
The light suits you.
这道光
This light here...
源自你帮我找到的火花
came from a spark that you helped me find.
黑暗很沉重
Darkness is heavy.
我们中有些人比别人背负得更多
Some of us carry more than others
那是因为我们够坚强  能承受得住
because we're strong enough to hold the weight.
但光是我们自己创造的
But we make the light.
光是你创造的  卡萝尔
You make the light, Carol.
你知道这点吧
You know that, don't you?
你知道我们不会复合吧
You know we're not getting back together, right?
你总是这么说
Yeah, you keep saying that.
以西结  我们需要你
Ezekiel, we need you back here!
阑尾破裂了
It burst, the appendix.
我们得送她去医院
We need to get her to a hospital.
不  没时间了
No, no. There's no time.
我们必须现在清理腹腔
Either we clean the abdomen now
不然会有腹膜炎
or peritonitis sets in.
转移她就太迟了
Move her and it will be too late.
我能做到  相信我
I can do this -- trust me.
我知道你能  我们怎么帮你
I know you can. How can we help?
以西结  你来用气囊
Ezekiel, take over bagging.
西奥  回医院拿更多抗生素
Uh, Theo, go back to the hospital, get more antibiotics.
拿着手术夹
Take this clamp,
稳住
hold tight.
拿着这个
Take this.
取更多纱布来
Get more gauze.
好  让我来
Alright, let me -- let me in there.
纱布
Gauze.
天啊
Oh, God.
好
Okay.
向后拉
Move it back.
再拉  再拉
Little further, little further.
好了
There it is.
纱布
Gauze.
很好  以西结
That's good, Ezekiel.
好
Okay.
现在清洗腹腔
Now we have to flush the cavity.
卡萝尔  盐水
Carol, saline.
接下来24个小时  我们会知道更多情况
We'll know more over the next 24 hours,
但看起来不错
but it looks good.
看吧
See?
小手术
Small procedure.
不必担心
Nothing to worry about.
能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
好
Yeah.
我后悔之前突然找了你
I, uh -- I regret my earlier ambush.
我实在太不应该了
It was mighty uncool of me.
如果你说的事真在这里发生了  那就太糟了
If the stuff that you mentioned is happening here, it's bad.
非常糟
Really bad.
我并非有意让你为难
Well, it was not my intention to put you in a tight spot.
如果这个安排让你感到不适的话...
If this arrangement makes you uncomfortable --
我是不适
It does.
正当我以为一切都要正常了
The idea of continuing to sneak around
又要偷偷摸摸做这种事...
just when I had hoped that things might go back to normal...
也许这真的不适合我
Maybe I'm not built for this.
但我别无选择
But I don't think I have a choice.
你当然有选择了
Of course you do.
我和朋友们会另寻途径的
My friends and I will find another avenue.
不
No.
尤金  我不是这个意思
Eugene, that's not what I meant.
我别无选择是因为
There is no choice because...
无法再回到正常了
there is no back to normal.
知道就是知道了
We know what we know.
因此事情必须改变
And because of that, things have to change.
我们不能等着别人站出来帮忙
I can't wait around for someone else to step up and help.
我可以向你保证
I can promise you this.
不管发现什么  不管遇到什么
Whatever we find, whatever comes our way,
你都不会独自面对
you will not face it alone.
无论发生什么  我都会在你身边
I'll be by your side, hell or high water.
你确定吗
You sure?
突破了命运的重重阻挠
Against all odds of the cosmos and humankind,
我们找到了彼此
we found one another.
我这辈子从没有对一件事如此确定过
I've never been more certain of anything in my life.
那么
So...
我该偷什么
what do I need to steal?
等等  别开火
Wait! Hold your fire!
我们是来谈话的
We're here to talk.
为了找你  我们长途跋涉
We've come a long way to find you.
要追踪你可真不容易
You were not easy to track down.
但既然你给我造成了这么多麻烦
But since you've caused me more than a handful of trouble,
那么你在杀我们之前
the least you can do is hear what I have to say
至少可以听我说句话
before you kill us.
快说
Talk fast.
我叫兰斯·霍恩斯比
My name is Lance Hornsby.
我是来为你提供工作的
And I'm here to offer you a job.